<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Main on Sc Online</title>
    <link>https://schafsam.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Main on Sc Online</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://schafsam.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB for Data-Intensive Applications</title>
      <link>https://schafsam.github.io/posts/mongodb-backend-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://schafsam.github.io/posts/mongodb-backend-engine/</guid>
      <description>MongoDB is scalable and schema-less NoSQL key-value storage, which makes it handy for applications to use as a persistent layer. The two features in this post views and change streams from MongoDB can turn your application into a full-fetched back-end engine for data-intensive applications.
Change Streams Since MongoDB 3.6 you can use change streams to create event-driven applications for data processing. Whenever an update occurs in a specific collection, MongoDB triggers a change event with the modified data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://schafsam.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://schafsam.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Me As a trained statistician with a passion for coding, I have honed my abilities to leverage data and drive insights. Python is my current go-to when it comes to programming languages, however, I am drawn to the power and potential of Rust. In my current role as a data scientist and machine learning engineer, I am constantly pushing the boundaries of what is possible with data-driven solutions.
The Page The post from https://juliasilge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://schafsam.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://schafsam.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Interests Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Natural Language Processsing (NLP), Python, Rust
Eudcation 2017 MSc in Statistics at the Seminar for Statistics from ETH Zürich</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
